famecount.com 2016-11-17

# Starcount - Bringing customers into the boardroom

## Privacy Policy

Starcount. manages a website and a range of mobile apps that enable fans to keep up with their favourite celebrities and brands on social media.

By connecting to our services we help you view your favourite stars’ most interesting social updates and news, from multiple sources, all in one place. We also keep track of your activities on social media to let you know how devoted a fan you are of your favourite stars. And our services also track the stars and brands themselves – ranking them and creating charts based on their social popularity and trends. We also operate business to business analytics services for brands, marketing agencies and others that use all the data we collect

This Privacy Policy explains how Starcount. collects, uses, discloses and processes your personal data. By visiting the Starcount. website or applications, authenticating with us or registering with us, or otherwise being provided an opportunity to view this Privacy Policy, you accept and consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

The data controller in respect of your personal data collected in accordance with this Privacy Policy is Starcount. Ltd (company number: 08004810) whose principal place of business is at Henry Wood House, 2 Riding House Street, London W1W 7FA

### Collection of personal data

The statistical and other social network data displayed on our website, www.starcount.com, and used across our various applications, products and services (the "Site"), relates to usage and trends within major social networks, such as Facebook, YouTube, Twitter, Google+, Sina Weibo, Tencent, Youku, Orkut, Mixi, VKontakte, Renren, Instagram and other services (the "Social Networks").

Any personal Social Network data we collect or use is either:

1) Publicly available from Social Networks without authentication (“Social Network Trend Data”): Celebrity and brand chart categorisations / biogs and other such data is derived from what is displayed publicly on the Social Networks or on other public sources such as Wikipedia and news reports. Additionally we track a range of underlying publicly available social media metrics, such as fan/ friend counts, engagement statistics and publicly available statistics on the connections between users on Social Networks. Currently anyone surfing the Internet can access this Social Network information we publish, from the websites themselves without registration, from search engines, and from any applications (such as ours) that utilise the APIs of these services. Your consent to our use of your publicly available data from the Social Networks being displayed on the Site is based on your privacy settings on the Social Networks themselves. If you do not wish for your data to appear on services like ours, the best solution is to change your privacy settings on the Social Networks themselves or, if not possible or preferred, to remove your accounts from those Social Networks. If, after changing privacy settings or deleting accounts on these Social Networks, you still for any reason notice personal data on the Site please contact us.

or

2) Non-Publicly Available Personal Data

Non-publicly available personal data (“Private Data”) that you have consented to provide to us for use on the Site by specifically and purposefully connecting to us via a Social Network or one of our third party partners' (“Partner”) websites ("Partner Websites").

If you authenticate with us using a Social Network or a Partner Website (for example, as part of the registration process for one of our applications ("Applications")) you will be asked as part of that process to make available certain personal information to us from those Social Networks or Partner Websites. By consenting to this process, you consent to provide your Private data to us and you consent to use of that Private Data by us. The Private Data that you share with us is determined by the consent you provide when you authenticate the relevant Application, but it may include, for example:

Your name, general demographic info, your location.

Your email address – if you have consented to provide this.

Your posts/content on Social Networks,

Lists of the stars and brands you follow and your interactions with stars and brands.

Your Social Network connections generally (who you are friends with, who you follow, who follows you etc).

We shall only use Private Data from Social Networks or Partner Websites where you have consented through this registration process. You may revoke such access at any time through the settings on the Site and the Applications. You may additionally request deletion or correction of your information at any time from our Applications by contacting us at [team@starcount.com](mailto:team@starcount.com).

We do not knowingly contact or collect Private Data from children under 14. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such Private Data, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or delete the Private Data.

### Other ways we may collect personal data

In addition to the Social Network Trend Data, which we collect and publish on Social Network charts/trends/audiences and the Private Data referred to above, we also may collect and process some personal data from general Site users in the day-to-day administration of the Site above and beyond the Social Network Trend Data. We may collect and process the following data about you:

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence

Details of transactions you carry out through the site

Details of your visits to the Site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data (see IP ADDRESSES and COOKIES, below).

### IP addresses and cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general Internet usage by using a cookie file, which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our Site and to deliver a better and more personalised service.

They may be used, for example:

To store information about your preferences and so allow us to customise the Site according to your individual interests.

To speed up your searches.

To recognise you when you return to our Site.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser, which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to the Site and by using the Site you consent to receiving these cookies for the purposes specified in this section.

If there are particular concerns you have with our Social Network Trend Data, data of users of the Site and data obtained from cookies, then please send an email for the attention of the Privacy Officer at [team@starcount.com](mailto:team@starcount.com).

### Where we store your Data

The personal data that we collect from you may be used, disclosed, transferred to, and stored at any location in which we operate, including outside the EEA, and may also be processed by third parties who will also be bound by these terms. By submitting or allowing us to collect your personal data, you agree to this transfer, disclosure, storage or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your personal data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. Further details on how we may disclose your personal data are set out below at “Disclosure of your Personal Information”.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password, which enables you to access certain parts of the Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal data transmitted to the Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your personal data, we will use strict procedures and security features to prevent unauthorised uses are made of the information.

### How We Use your Data

### Social Network Trend Data

Our Social Network Trend Data and content may be published and shared in our web applications at www.starcount.com, on our mobile and other applications and in any reports we produce on third party sites, publications and applications, and in any B2B applications and products, operated by us or our Partners or licensees.

### Private Data

We, or our Partners, may contact you only where you have shared Private Data with us (either directly or through authenticating with one or more Social Networks). We may contact you, for example, to:

Send you information relating to our products or, where you have consented, our Partners’ products;

Invite you to take part in competitions and contests;

Send you information related to your activities in our applications;

Inform you of and invite you to take advantage of offers, rewards and privileges;

Inform you of other products, which we think may be of interest to you (in the case of third party products, where you have opted in to receiving such information);

You may always opt out of such communications by following the instructions on those messages or (where the contact is through a Social Network) through revoking your connection with our applications.

WE WILL NEVER USE, NOR SHARE YOUR INFORMATION FOR THE PURPOSES OF BULK UNSOLICITED MAIL SENT BY PARTIES UNCONNECTED TO Starcount. OR ITS PARTNERS.

### Other personal data

General Site user information may be used in the following ways:

To ensure that content from the Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you. By connecting with the Site you consent to this communication. For the avoidance of doubt we will not send any messages to you unless they are about our services or are messages from our Partners or Partner Websites.

You may opt out of such messages at any time through the unsubscribe option on these messages.

To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

To allow you to participate in interactive features of the Site, when you choose to do so.

To notify you about changes to our service.

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users, or use aggregate information to help target advertisements more appropriately.

### Disclosure of your information

In connection with the uses made of information, above, we may disclose or transfer your personal information to any member of our company, or related holding company/subsidiaries. These may be located outside the EEA in jurisdictions which do not have equivalent data protection laws to those in your jurisdiction.

We may also disclose or transfer your personal information to third parties for the following purposes:

In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

If our Site is acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal or business obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements;

### Accessing and updating your personal information

Unless a derogation applies, we will comply with requests to access or correct your personal data. We will also ensure personal data is accurate and complete. Where reasonably requested, we will also cease to retain personal data or remove the means by which personal data can be associated with individuals.

### Links

Our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from websites of our Partners, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

### Variations

We may revise our privacy policy at any time by amending this page. You are expected to check this page from time to time to take notice of any changes we made. Some of the provisions contained in our privacy policy may also be superseded by provisions or notices published elsewhere on the Site. If we make any changes to this policy, which are, in our sole discretion, material, we will notify you by publishing these changes prominently on the Site.

### Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed. Please contact us at [team@starcount.com](mailto:team@starcount.com).
